Guide to the Class of 1955, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Class of 1955, Yale College, records
1955-2003
RU 324
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
840.94
The records consist of minutes, photographs, audio CD, and other records of the Yale College Class of 1955.
Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1955
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 10-A (YRG 10-A), Records of Yale College classes.
Conditions Governing Access
Access is partially restricted. See inventory for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of minutes, photographs, audio CD, and other records of the Yale College Class of 1955.
Photographs; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1955; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae
- Records of the Class of 1955, 1995-1996; Accession 1997-A-065
  - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Minutes of the Class of 1955, 1995-2001; Accession 2002-A-055
  - Minutes, 1995-2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Memorabilia of the Class of 1955, circa 2000; Accession 2004-A-194
  - Reunion button, circa 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Reunion records for the Class of 1955, 2003; Accession 2005-A-017
  - Yale 1955 London reunion, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Assorted photographs, some of which were published in the "Yale Daily News", circa 1955; Accession 2005-A-173
  - Photographs, circa 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- "Our Music" [sound recording], Yale College, Class of 1955, 50th Reunion, 2005; Accession 2005-A-184
  Conditions Governing Access
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  - "Our Music", 2005; compact disc (Box 1)